{
	"sports":
	[
		{
			"_id":1,
			"Question":"Subroto cup is associated with",
			"OptionA":"Cricket",
			"OptionB":"Football",
			"OptionC":"Chess",
			"OptionD":"Golf",
			"Answer":"B"
		},
		{
			"_id":2,
			"Question":"2014 FIFA World Cup was  held in",
			"OptionA":"London",
			"OptionB":"Brazil",
			"OptionC":"India",
			"OptionD":"Germany",
			"Answer":"A"
		},
		{
			"_id":3,
			"Question":"2010 winter Olympic were held in",
			"OptionA":" USA",
			"OptionB":"Russia",
			"OptionC":"Vancouver",
			"OptionD":"Australia",
			"Answer":"C"
		},
		{
			"_id":4,
			"Question":"Wilson Jones is associated with",
			"OptionA":" Hockey",
			"OptionB":"Golf",
			"OptionC":"Billiards",
			"OptionD":" Air–race",
			"Answer":"C"
		},
		{
			"_id":5,
			"Question":"The term “Slam” is associated with",
			"OptionA":"Cricket",
			"OptionB":"Tennis",
			"OptionC":"Boxing",
			"OptionD":"Football",
			"Answer":"B"
		},
		{
			"_id":6,
			"Question":"Which county did Ravi Shastri play for",
			"OptionA":"Glamorgan",
			"OptionB":"Leicestershire",
			"OptionC":"Gloucestershire",
			"OptionD":"Lancashire",
			"Answer":"A"
		},
		{
			"_id":7,
			"Question":"First Indian to win the World Amateur Billiards title",
			"OptionA":"Geet Sethi",
			"OptionB":"Wilson Jones",
			"OptionC":"Michael Ferreira",
			"OptionD":"Manoj Kothari",
			"Answer":"B"
		},
		{
			"_id":8,
			"Question":"The term“Googly” is associated with",
			"OptionA":"Cricket",
			"OptionB":"Football",
			"OptionC":"Badminton",
			"OptionD":"Hockey",
			"Answer":"A"
		},
		{
			"_id":9,
			"Question":"Krishna Poonia is associated with",
			"OptionA":"Football",
			"OptionB":"Hockey",
			"OptionC":"Chess",
			"OptionD":" Athletics",
			"Answer":"D"
		},
		{
			"_id":10,
			"Question":"In 1924 the first winter Olympics was held in",
			"OptionA":"Italy",
			"OptionB":" France",
			"OptionC":"Austria",
			"OptionD":"Canada",
			"Answer":"B"
		},
		{
			"_id":11,
			"Question":"Ricky Ponting is also known as",
			"OptionA":"The Rickster",
			"OptionB":"Ponts",
			"OptionC":"Ponter",
			"OptionD":"Punter",
			"Answer":"D"
		},
		{
			"_id":12,
			"Question":"Ronaldo is associated with",
			"OptionA":"Cricket",
			"OptionB":"Football",
			"OptionC":"Hockey",
			"OptionD":"Tennis",
			"Answer":"B"
		},
		{
			"_id":13,
			"Question":"Nickname of Glenn McGrath is",
			"OptionA":"Ooh Ahh",
			"OptionB":"Penguin",
			"OptionC":"Big Bird",
			"OptionD":"Pigeon",
			"Answer":"D"
		},
		{
			"_id":14,
			"Question":"Mark Waugh is commonly called",
			"OptionA":"Afganistan",
			"OptionB":"Junior",
			"OptionC":"Tugga",
			"OptionD":"Julio",
			"Answer":"A"
		},
		{
			"_id":15,
			"Question":"India won its first Olympic hockey gold in",
			"OptionA":"1928",
			"OptionB":"1932",
			"OptionC":"1936",
			"OptionD":"1948",
			"Answer":"A"
		},
		{
			"_id":16,
			"Question":"Who won the 1993 \"King of the Ring\"",
			"OptionA":"Owen Hart",
			"OptionB":"Bret Hart",
			"OptionC":"Edge",
			"OptionD":"Mabel",
			"Answer":"B"
		},
		{
			"_id":17,
			"Question":"Yankee Stadium in Newyork is associated with",
			"OptionA":" Cricket",
			"OptionB":"Tennis",
			"OptionC":"Boxing",
			"OptionD":"Hockey",
			"Answer":"C"
		},
		{
			"_id":18,
			"Question":"Wankhede Stadium is at",
			"OptionA":"New Delhi",
			"OptionB":"Chennai",
			"OptionC":"Mumbai",
			"OptionD":"Kolkata",
			"Answer":"C"
		},
		{
			"_id":19,
			"Question":"1st ODI captain for India",
			"OptionA":"Ajit Wadekar",
			"OptionB":"Bishen Singh Bedi",
			"OptionC":"Nawab Pataudi",
			"OptionD":"Vinoo Mankad",
			"Answer":"A"
		},
		{
			"_id":20,
			"Question":"First hand glider was designed by",
			"OptionA":"Leonardo DaVinci",
			"OptionB":"The Wright brothers",
			"OptionC":"Francis Rogallo",
			"OptionD":"Galileo",
			"Answer":"A"
		},
		{
			"_id":21,
			"Question":"The 'Dronacharya Award' is given to",
			"OptionA":"Sportsmen",
			"OptionB":"Coaches",
			"OptionC":"Umpires",
			"OptionD":"Sports Editors",
			"Answer":"B"
		},
		{
			"_id":22,
			"Question":"Term associated with chess",
			"OptionA":"Pitcher",
			"OptionB":"Deuce",
			"OptionC":"Vulnerable",
			"OptionD":"Gambit",
			"Answer":"D"
		},
		{
			"_id":23,
			"Question":"1st ODI match played in India at",
			"OptionA":"New Delhi",
			"OptionB":"Ahmedabad",
			"OptionC":"Kolkata",
			"OptionD":"Mumbai",
			"Answer":"B"
		},
		{
			"_id":24,
			"Question":"First youth Olympic games was held in",
			"OptionA":"Japan",
			"OptionB":"China",
			"OptionC":"Singapore",
			"OptionD":"North Korea",
			"Answer":"C"
		},
		{
			"_id":25,
			"Question":"Hurlington stadium is associated with",
			"OptionA":"Golf",
			"OptionB":"Boxing",
			"OptionC":"Cricket",
			"OptionD":"Polo",
			"Answer":"D"
		},
	]
}